Amanda Seals Show, today's
goes to a Philadelphia officer and brotherly love.
This Philadelphia officer went viral for cuffing his alleged twin brother.
So one brother hauls the other out of a home, both grinning, you know, like they in a family photo.
The arresting officer had this look on his face that's like, you knew this would come down to this, right?
Like, you know, when we was at the cookout two months ago, like we knew that this was inevitable.
And then the other one is like yelling, I'll be right home, free food.
So I've heard of playing cops and robbers, but this is OD.
This is OD.
But if you got to do the perp walk, might as well do it with someone who loves you and looks just like you.
Today's letdown goes to unused potential.
Now, a porch pirate was caught on surveillance, stealing a package from a man's porch,
but he wasn't like a cat burglar, you know, or some acrobatic Chilean.
No, he was dressed in a trash bag.
So basically, this man went full on Oscar the Grouch, rolled up to the scene of the crime,
wrapped in a black trash bag like it was Glad Cthulhu or, you know, Kanye.
And then in the video, you can see a trash bag like waddle onto the porch,
nab the package and then shuffle away.
I just feel like if you have that much commitment to something,
you should be using those powers for good.
You could be using those powers for good.
This is not using your potential to the fullest.
And that's something we should all be trying to do.
We are, we are, we are.